<?xml version="1.0"  encoding="UTF-8"?>

    <preferences xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="index.xsd">
	
	 <author>
		<name>Jedrzej</name>
		<surname>Alicki</surname>
		<group>2</group>
   </author>
	
	<drivers>
		<driver number="21" podiums="xx" team="Williams"> Gorge Russel</driver>
		<driver number="20" podiums="xx" team="Williams">Nicholas Latifi</driver>
		<driver number="xx" podiums="xx" team="Haas">Kevin Magnusen</driver>
		<driver number="cc" podiums="xx" team="Haas">Romain Grosjean</driver>
		<driver number="xx" podiums="xx" team="AlfaRomeo">Kimi Raikonen</driver>
		<driver number="xx" podiums="xx" team="AlfaRomeo">Antonio Govinazzi</driver>
		<driver number="xx" podiums="xx" team="RacingPoint">Sergio Perez</driver>
		<driver number="xx" podiums="xx" team="RacingPoint">Lance Stroll</driver>
		<driver number="xx" podiums="xx" team="AlphaTauri">Piere Gasly</driver>
		<driver number="xx" podiums="xx" team="AlphaTauri">Danil Kvyat</driver>
		<driver number="xx" podiums="xx" team="Ferrari">Sebastian Vettel</driver>
		<driver number="xx" podiums="xx" team="Ferrari">Charles Leclerc</driver>
		<driver number="xx" podiums="xx" team="Rentaul">Esteban Ocon</driver>
		<driver number="xx" podiums="xx" team="Rentaul">Daniel Ricardo</driver>
		<driver number="xx" podiums="xx" team="RedBull">Alex Albon</driver>
		<driver number="xx" podiums="xx" team="RedBull">Max Verstappen</driver>
		<driver number="xx" podiums="xx" team="Mclaren">LandoNorris</driver>
		<driver number="xx" podiums="xx" team="Mclaren">Carlos Sainz</driver>
		<driver number="xx" podiums="xx" team="Mercedes">Valtteri Bottas</driver>
		<driver number="xx" podiums="xx" team="Mercedes"> Lewis Hamilton</driver>
	</drivers>

		<facts kind="informations" current="yes">
		<text>
			Formula One (also known as Formula 1 or F1) is the highest class of international single-seater auto racing 
			sanctioned by the Fédération Internationale de l'Automobile (FIA) and owned by Liberty Media, an American mass media company, 
			through its wholly owned subsidiary, the Formula One Group. The World Drivers' Championship, which became the FIA Formula One World Championship
			in 1981, has been one of the premier forms of racing around the world since its inaugural season in 1950. The word "formula" in the name 
			refers to the set of rules to which all participants' cars must conform. A Formula One season consists of a series of races, known as Grands
			Prix (French for ''grand prizes' or 'great prizes''), which take place worldwide on purpose-built circuits and on closed public roads.
		</text>
		</facts>
	
		<facts kind="rules" current="yes">
			<rule>The “One Move” Defending Rule</rule>
			<rule>Drivers Must Qualify Within 107% Of The Pole-Sitter</rule>
			<rule>If an engine part is changed, they take a grid drop penalty</rule>
			<rule>Speeding In The Pitlane? You Get A Penalty</rule>
			<rule>They Must Change Tyre Compounds In The Race</rule>
			<rule>Safety Car Line Overtaking</rule>
			<rule>Rain Lights MUST Be Used In The Wet</rule>
		</facts>
		
		<facts kind="car" current="yes">
		<text>
			A Formula One car is a single-seat, open cockpit, open-wheel racing car with substantial front and rear wings,
			and an engine positioned behind the driver, intended to be used in competition at Formula One racing events. 
			The regulations governing the cars are unique to the championship and specify that cars must be constructed by the racing teams themselves,
			though the design and manufacture can be outsourced.
			Modern-day Formula One cars are constructed from composites of carbon fibre and similar ultra-lightweight materials.
			The minimum weight permissible is 740 kg (1,631 lb) including the driver but not fuel. Cars are weighed with dry-weather tyres fitted. 
			Prior to the 2014 F1 season, cars often weighed in under this limit so teams added ballast in order to add weight to the car.
			The advantage of using ballast is that it can be placed anywhere in the car to provide ideal weight distribution.
			This can help lower the car's centre of gravity to improve stability and also allows the team to fine-tune the weight distribution 
			of the car to suit individual circuits. 
			</text>
		</facts>
		
		
		
	
	
	
	
	
		